motivosity.com 2015-04-20

# Privacy Policy

Last Updated 5/18/2014

Introduction

This Privacy Policy explains what information Motivosity, Inc collects about you and why, what we do with that information, how we share it, and how we handle the content you place in our products and services.

Scope of Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the information that we obtain through your use of Motivosity via a "Device" or when you otherwise interact with Motivosity.

"Motivosity Service" include our website and SaaS application, but does not include:

• Motivosity products or services for which a separate privacy policy is provided.

• Third party products. These are third party products or services that you may choose to integrate with Motivosity.

A "Device" is any computer used to access the Motivosity Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device.

By registering for or using Motivosity Service you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy.

Definitions

**Motivosity Service** : Motivosity’s website and SaaS Products

**Content** : any information or data that you upload, submit, post, create, transmit, store or display in a Motivosity Service.

**Information** : all of the different forms of data, content, and information collected by us as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information** : information that may be used to readily identify or contact you as an individual person, such as: name, address, email address, or phone number. Personal Information does not include information that has been anonymized such that it does not allow for the ready identification of specific individuals. 

**SaaS Products** : Motivosity’s OnDemand hosted solution as well as other Motivosity hosted solutions that display a link to this Privacy Policy. For the avoidance of doubt, if a Motivosity hosted solution displays a link to a different privacy policy, then that other privacy policy shall apply.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, where appropriate we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the login screen or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use Motivosity Service to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy, you will need to stop using Motivosity Service and deactivate your account(s).

Information you provide to us

**Account and Profile Information** : We collect information about you and your company as you register for an account, create or modify your profile, make purchases through, use, access, or interact with Motivosity Service (including but not limited to when you upload, download, collaborate on or share Content). Information we collect includes but is not limited to your name, username, address, email address, phone number, profile photo, job title, or credit card details. You may provide this information directly when you enter it in Motivosity Service, or in some cases another user (such as a system administrator) creating an account on your behalf may provide it (most commonly when your company requests that you use our products). If you are providing information (including Personal Information) about someone else, you confirm that you have the authority to act for them and to consent to the collection and use of their Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Content** : We collect and store Content that you create, input, submit, post, upload, transmit, store or display in the process of using our SaaS Products or Website. Such Content includes any Personal Information or other sensitive information that you choose to include (“passively-collected Personal Information”).

**Other submissions** : We collect other data that you submit to our Website or as you participate in any interactive features of the Motivosity website or customer support experience.

Information we collect from your use of Motivosity Service

**Web Logs** : As is true with most websites and services delivered over the Internet, we gather certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Website and SaaS Products. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses as well as browser type, internet service provider, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, information you search for, locale and language preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, and system configuration information. In the case of our SaaS Product, the URLs you accessed (and therefore included in our log files) include names and tokenized data relating to information in your organization as necessary for the SaaS Product to perform the requested operations. Occasionally, we may connect Personal Information to information gathered in our log files as necessary to improve Motivosity Service for individual customers.

**Analytics Information from Website and SaaS Products** : We and our analytics provider collect and store analytics information when you use our Website and SaaS Products to help us improve our products and services. In the Saas Products, this analytics information consists of the feature and function of the Motivosity Service being used, the username and IP address of the individual who is using the feature or function (which will include Personal Information if the Personal Information was incorporated into the username), the sizes and original filenames of attachments, and additional information required to detail the operation of the function and which parts of the Motivosity Service are being affected. 

We currently use NewRelic as an analytics provider. To learn more about the privacy policy of NewRelic, refer to http://newrelic.com/privacy.

**Analytics Information Derived from Content** : Analytics information also consists of data we collect as a result of running queries against Content across our user base for the purposes of generating Usage Data. "Usage Data" is aggregated data about a group or category of services, features or users that does not contain Personal Information.

Though we may happen upon sensitive or Personal Information as we compile Usage Data from Content across user instances, this is a byproduct of our efforts to understand broader patterns and trends. It is not a concerted effort by us to examine the Content of any particular customer.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies** : We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies that we save to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We use cookies to improve and customize the Motivosity Service and your experience; to allow you to access and use the Website or SaaS Products without re-entering your username or password; and to count visits and understand which areas and features of the Website and SaaS Products are most popular. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of our Website or SaaS Products. 

How we use Information we collect

**General Uses** : We use the information we collect about you (including Personal Information to the extent applicable) for a variety of purposes, including to:

• Provide, operate, maintain, improve, and promote Motivosity Service;

• Enable you to access and use Motivosity Service, including uploading, downloading, collaborating on and sharing Content;

• Process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices;

• Communicate with you, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; providing customer service and support; providing you with information about services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests and events; providing other news or information about us and our select partners; and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages. Generally, you have the ability to opt out of receiving any promotional communications as described below under “Your Choices”;

• Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with Motivosity Service and for marketing or advertising purposes;

• Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorized access to Motivosity Service, and other illegal activities;

• Personalize Motivosity Service, including by providing content, features, or advertisements that match your interests and preferences;

• Enable you to communicate, collaborate, and share Content with users you designate; and

• For other purposes about which we notify you.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, we will not use Personal Information appearing in our Analytics Logs or Web Logs for any purpose.

**Aggregate Information** : Motivosity may compile aggregated usage profiles to help its subscribers better understand best practices concerning particular activities and their impact on company culture and employee satisfaction. This aggregated information is based on general trends across an entire population of companies and is in no way tied to a specific individual or organization. This compiled aggregate information may appear in the Motivosity application to provide guidance to Service Subscribers. It may also appear in sales and promotional materials detailing the impact the Motivosity Service can have on companies.

Information sharing and disclosure

We will not share or disclose any of your Personal Information or Content with third parties except as described in this policy. We do not sell your Personal Information or Content.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests** Protection of Our Rights: We will not disclose your Information (including your Personal Information) to any third party without your consent.

Business Transfers: We may share or transfer your information (including your Personal Information) in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

**Aggregated or Anonymized Data** : We may share aggregated or anonymized information as described above.

With Your Consent. We will share your personal information with third parties when we have your consent to do so.

Information we do not share

We do not share Personal Information about you with third parties for their marketing purposes (including direct marketing purposes) without your permission.
